Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪My heart shattered, withered into pieces♪
♪تحطم قلبي، ذبل إلى قطع♪
♪Yet I still can't find a trace of you♪
♪ولكنني لا أزال غير قادر على العثور على أي أثر لك♪
♪Like a whale drowning in the cracks of the deep sea♪
♪مثل حوت يغرق في شقوق البحر العميق♪
♪Thinking of you, I lose myself completely♪
♪أفكر فيك، وأفقد نفسي تمامًا♪
♪My heart shattered, withered into pieces♪
♪تحطم قلبي، ذبل إلى قطع♪
♪Humbly, I still long to search for you♪
♪بكل تواضع، ما زلت أتوق للبحث عنك♪
♪Screaming as I fall into the darkest abyss♪
♪أصرخ وأنا أسقط في الهاوية المظلمة♪
♪Echoing back is only the tide of loneliness♪
♪العودة إلى الوراء ليست سوى موجة الوحدة♪
♪Overestimating myself♪
♪المبالغة في تقدير نفسي♪
=Marry Him in Her Place=
=تزوجيه مكانها=
=Episode 15=
=الحلقة 15=
The sky over Rong City is about to fully brighten.
السماء فوق مدينة رونغ على وشك أن تصبح مشرقة بالكامل.
It requires the guns of the police station
يتطلب الأمر بنادق مركز الشرطة
and the influence of the Chengyun Society,
وتأثير جمعية تشنغيون،
neither can be missing.
لا يمكن أن يكون أي منهما مفقودًا.
Unfortunately, the sky over Rong City is shrouded in smoke and chaos.
لسوء الحظ، السماء فوق مدينة رونغ مغطاة بالدخان والفوضى.
I really cannot stand by idly.
أنا حقا لا أستطيع الوقوف مكتوف الأيدي.
Since when did the underworld maintain justice?
منذ متى حافظ العالم السفلي على العدالة؟
What a joke.
يا لها من مزحة!
White has turned to black.
تحول الأبيض إلى الأسود.
The world is upside down.
العالم مقلوب رأسا على عقب.
Chief Song.
رئيس الأغنية.
Who is truly the laughable one?
من هو المضحك حقا؟
Brothers quarrel at home.
يتشاجرون الإخوة في المنزل.
It only allows outsiders to take advantage.
فهو يسمح فقط للغرباء بالاستفادة.
That must never happen.
هذا لا يجب أن يحدث أبدًا.
Lin Yun.
لين يون.
I already scolded Zhichu.
لقد وبخت زيتشو بالفعل.
This matter was handled improperly by him.
لقد تعامل مع هذه المسألة بشكل غير لائق.
Regarding those petty criminals
فيما يتعلق بهؤلاء المجرمين الصغار
doing despicable things right under his nose,
القيام بأشياء حقيرة تحت أنفه مباشرة،
and he was completely unaware.
ولم يكن على علم بذلك على الإطلاق.
You went straight to the core
لقد ذهبت مباشرة إلى الجوهر
which is truly a great achievement.
وهو إنجاز عظيم حقًا.
It was Zhichu who misunderstood at first
كان Zhichu هو الذي أساء الفهم في البداية
and causing a misunderstanding.
وتسبب سوء الفهم.
A misunderstanding?
سوء فهم؟
It seems you have made your judgment, Mayor Song.
يبدو أنك قد أصدرت حكمك، يا عمدة سونغ.
You two are both eager to do good,
كلاكما حريص على فعل الخير،
both for the sake of Rong City.
كلاهما من أجل مدينة رونغ.
Today I will host.
اليوم سأستضيف.
First, to apologize on behalf of Zhichu to you.
أولاً، أود أن أعتذر لك نيابة عن Zhichu.
Second, as mayor,
ثانياً، بصفتي عمدة،
to thank you both for joining forces to cleanse Rong City of smoke and filth.
لشكركما على توحيد جهودكما لتطهير مدينة رونغ من الدخان والأوساخ.
Come.
يأتي.
Mayor Song.
أغنية رئيسية.
Let me speak fairly.
دعني أتحدث بشكل عادل.
How can a father apologize on behalf of his son?
كيف يمكن للأب أن يعتذر عن ابنه؟
This guilt must be repaid personally to show sincerity.
يجب سداد هذا الذنب شخصيًا لإظهار الصدق.
Lin Yun.
لين يون.
Your wife really has a sharp tongue.
زوجتك لديها لسان حاد حقا.
Zhichu.
تشيتشو.
The words have been spoken to this extent.
وقد قيلت الكلمات إلى هذا الحد.
Let's see how you respond.
دعونا نرى كيف تستجيب.
Is that enough?
هل هذا كافي؟
Chief Song.
رئيس الأغنية.
I have been tortured and bled.
لقد تعرضت للتعذيب والنزيف.
Can a cup of wine really smooth over all grudges?
هل يمكن لكأس من النبيذ أن يخفف حقا من كل الضغائن؟
Is this enough now?
هل هذا يكفي الآن؟
Fine, let's consider this a blood oath.
حسنًا، دعونا نعتبر هذا قسمًا بالدم.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
your brotherly bond is solidified.
لقد تعززت رابطة الأخوة بينكم.
No longer speaking as two separate families.
لم يعد يتحدثون كعائلتين منفصلتين.
Work together
العمل معا
to build Rong City.
لبناء مدينة رونغ.
Master. Your secretary is looking for you.
سيدي، سكرتيرتك تبحث عنك.
Official duties call.
نداء الواجبات الرسمية.
I'll take my leave first.
سوف آخذ إجازتي أولاً.
You two brothers can catch up properly.
يمكنكم يا أخواني اللحاق ببعضكم البعض بشكل صحيح.
Madam Lin seems to really enjoy eating fish eyes.
يبدو أن السيدة لين تستمتع حقًا بتناول عيون السمك.
What a coincidence.
يا لها من مصادفة!
Liang Yi also likes eating fish eyes.
ليانغ يي يحب أيضًا تناول عيون السمك.
Wrong guess.
تخمين خاطئ.
It's my husband who likes eating them.
زوجي هو الذي يحب أكلها.
She
هي
has figured out my tastes completely.
لقد فهمت أذواقي بشكل كامل.
There's just one left.
بقي واحد فقط.
What?
ماذا؟
Has Madam Song changed her taste?
هل تغيرت ذوق السيدة سونغ؟
I heard that once a woman is pregnant,
سمعت أنه بمجرد أن تصبح المرأة حاملاً،
her tastes will change.
سوف تتغير أذواقها.
It can't be
لا يمكن أن يكون
Madam Song
السيدة سونغ
has become a mother?
أصبحت أمًا؟
My wife and I are of one mind.
أنا وزوجتي على رأي واحد.
Even if she is to become a mother,
حتى لو أصبحت أمًا،
I will take good care of her.
سأعتني بها جيدا.
No need for you to worry, Madam Lin.
لا داعي للقلق، سيدتي لين.
I heard that last time Madam Lin went to the pharmacy warehouse
سمعت أن آخر مرة ذهبت فيها السيدة لين إلى مستودع الصيدلية
was just to take a look at the Five-lobed Coptis.
كان الأمر مجرد إلقاء نظرة على القبطي ذو الخمسة فصوص.
Five-lobed Coptis is extremely rare.
يعتبر القبطيس ذو الخمسة فصوص نادرًا للغاية.
I was just curious.
لقد كنت مجرد فضولي.
But that the Liang family warehouse has Five-lobed Coptis,
لكن مستودع عائلة ليانغ يحتوي على قبطيات ذات خمسة فصوص،
besides the Liang family manager, only my father-in-law and my wife know.
باستثناء مدير عائلة ليانغ، فقط حمي وزوجتي يعرفان الأمر.
Where did you hear that?
أين سمعت ذلك؟
As the top pharmacy in Rong City, the Liang family
باعتبارها الصيدلية الأولى في مدينة رونغ، عائلة ليانغ
must have some rare herbs.
يجب أن يكون هناك بعض الأعشاب النادرة.
It was just a coincidence.
لقد كانت مجرد مصادفة.
There are so many rare herbs.
هناك العديد من الأعشاب النادرة.
You asked casually,
لقد سألت عرضا،
and happened to ask about one that was in the warehouse.
وصادف أن سألت عن واحد كان في المستودع.
What a coincidence.
يا لها من مصادفة!
We were invited to dinner,
لقد تمت دعوتنا لتناول العشاء،
not for interrogation.
ليس للاستجواب.
Farewell.
وداع.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Perhaps Yunzhou also got the news,
ربما حصل يونزو أيضًا على الأخبار،
afraid we'd cut off the opium trade.
خائفون من أن نقطع تجارة الأفيون.
Go tell them.
اذهب وأخبرهم.
The opium trade is only paused.
لقد تم إيقاف تجارة الأفيون فقط.
But every cent owed will still be paid.
ولكن كل سنت مستحق سيتم دفعه.
This...
هذا...
Can be considered tribute.
يمكن اعتبارها تكريمًا.
We must maintain the Yunzhou route.
يجب علينا الحفاظ على طريق يونزو.
I'm pointing at their guns.
أنا أشير إلى بنادقهم.
Song Zhichu was clearly suspicious just now.
كان سونغ تشيتشو يشك بوضوح في هذه اللحظة.
So we must act quickly.
لذا يتعين علينا التحرك بسرعة.
Have Lu Man's son and husband been found?
هل تم العثور على ابن لو مان وزوجها؟
They've been rescued.
لقد تم انقاذهم.
Song Zhichu locked them
سونغ تشيتشو أغلقهم
in his private residence in the east of the city.
في مسكنه الخاص شرقي المدينة.
This father and son are his weakness.
هذا الأب والابن هما ضعفه.
In our hands, they are trump cards.
في أيدينا، هم أوراق رابحة.
We must expose Lu Man's identity quickly.
يجب علينا الكشف عن هوية لو مان بسرعة.
Song Zhichu won't give us much time.
لن يمنحنا سونغ تشيتشو الكثير من الوقت.
In a few days, Song Ming
في غضون أيام قليلة، سونغ مينغ
will host this year's charity banquet with the Chamber of Commerce.
سوف تستضيف حفل العشاء الخيري لهذا العام مع غرفة التجارة.
All the prominent merchants in the city
جميع التجار البارزين في المدينة
will attend in person.
سوف يحضر شخصيا.
Song Ming wants to run for provincial chairman.
سونغ مينغ يريد الترشح لمنصب رئيس المقاطعة.
He can't do it without their support.
لا يمكنه القيام بذلك بدون دعمهم.
What's your plan?
ما هي خطتك؟
Just be Madam Lin, calmly.
فقط كوني السيدة لين، بهدوء.
I said
قلت
the Song family matter is for me to handle.
مسألة عائلة سونغ هي من اختصاصي.
I once had the same dress.
لقد كان عندي نفس الفستان ذات مرة.
It was made following your style.
لقد تم صنعه وفقًا لأسلوبك.
Yan's Tailor Shop.
محل خياطة يان.
Yan's?
يان؟
Sir.
سيد.
These cufflinks I ordered three days ago.
لقد طلبت هذه الأزرار منذ ثلاثة أيام.
You have good taste, Miss.
لديك ذوق جيد، يا آنسة.
This lady truly has an eye for treasures.
هذه السيدة لديها حقا عين للكنوز.
These cufflinks are brand new arrivals today.
هذه أزرار الأكمام هي من المنتجات الجديدة اليوم.
♪Leaning on each other in the cold wind♪
♪الاعتماد على بعضنا البعض في الرياح الباردة♪
All's fair in war.
كل شيء جائز في الحرب.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
♪Walking together for so long♪
♪المشي معًا لفترة طويلة♪
Little Fox.
ثعلب صغير.
♪When we met again, snow was settling on our shoulders♪
♪عندما التقينا مرة أخرى، كان الثلج يستقر على أكتافنا♪
So it's you.
إذن أنت.
How do you remember what I wore?
كيف تتذكر ما كنت أرتديه؟
♪I never thought that in this moment too♪
♪لم أفكر في ذلك في هذه اللحظة أيضًا♪
♪We'd get a brief taste of growing old together♪
♪سنحصل على لمحة سريعة عن الشيخوخة معًا♪
♪Yet we can't hold each other or stay together anymore♪
♪ولكننا لا نستطيع أن نحتضن بعضنا البعض أو أن نبقى معًا بعد الآن♪
You're not Xu Yin.
أنت لست شو يين.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Chief Song, what do you mean by that?
الرئيس سونغ، ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
I've already checked.
لقد قمت بالتحقق بالفعل.
Xu Yin died on the first day you entered Huaying Brothel.
لقد ماتت Xu Yin في اليوم الأول الذي دخلت فيه بيت الدعارة Huaying.
Nothing can really be hidden from you.
لا يمكن إخفاء أي شيء عنك حقًا.
I really am not Xu Yin.
أنا لست حقا شو يين.
Why pretend to be her?
لماذا تتظاهر بأنك هي؟
Because of jealousy.
بسبب الغيرة.
Lin Yun is the boss of the Chengyun Society.
لين يون هو رئيس جمعية تشنغيون.
If I pretend to be Xu Yin, I can get everything I want.
إذا تظاهرت بأنني Xu Yin، يمكنني الحصول على كل ما أريد.
This deal is guaranteed profit.
هذه الصفقة مضمونة الربح.
If Lin Yun finds out,
إذا اكتشف لين يون ذلك،
I'm dead.
انا ميت.
I hope you will show mercy, Chief Song.
أتمنى أن تظهر الرحمة، يا رئيس سونغ.
Let me go.
دعني أذهب.
Why should I help you?
لماذا يجب علي أن أساعدك؟
Unless...
إلا إذا...
Unless what?
إلا ماذا؟
Unless you come with me.
إلا إذا أتيت معي.
Don't be afraid.
لا تخف.
I won't hurt you.
لن أؤذيك.
As long as you follow me, everything Lin Yun can give you,
طالما أنك تتبعني، كل ما يمكن أن يقدمه لك لين يون،
I can also give you.
وأستطيع أن أعطيك أيضاً.
Even more than him.
حتى أكثر منه.
I want the Liang family too. Will you give it to me?
أريد عائلة ليانغ أيضًا. هل ستعطيني إياها؟
What?
ماذا؟
You get scared
أنت تشعر بالخوف
just because I'm serious?
فقط لأنني جاد؟
The Liang family is nothing.
عائلة ليانغ ليست شيئا.
So generous.
كريم جداً.
What exactly
ماذا بالضبط
caught your attention, Chief Song?
هل لفت انتباهك يا رئيس سونغ؟
Because you understand me.
لأنك تفهمني.
Chief Song.
رئيس الأغنية.
I ate a bit too much today.
لقد أكلت كثيرًا اليوم.
Don't make me feel sick.
لا تجعلني أشعر بالمرض.
Don't shamelessly push your luck.
لا تضغط على حظك بلا خجل.
Who exactly are you?
من أنت بالضبط؟
Why are you in my room?
لماذا أنت في غرفتي؟
What happened to your neck wound?
ماذا حدث لجرح رقبتك؟
Where have you been?
أين كنت؟
(Invitation: Lin Yun, Song Ming cordially invite)
(دعوة: لين يون، سونغ مينغ يدعوان بحرارة)
- Song Ming's invitation has arrived. - What exactly happened?
- وصلت دعوة سونغ مينغ. - ماذا حدث بالضبط؟
Song Zhichu knows I'm not Xu Yin.
يعرف Song Zhichu أنني لست Xu Yin.
You encountered Song Zhichu?
هل واجهت أغنية Zhichu؟
He caused the injury?
هو الذي تسبب في الإصابة؟
The main point now is we must ensure
النقطة الرئيسية الآن هي أننا يجب أن نضمن
tomorrow's plan goes perfectly.
خطة الغد تسير على ما يرام.
You're already exposed.
لقد تعرضت بالفعل للخطر.
Do you think Song Zhichu will let you go?
هل تعتقد أن سونغ تشيتشو سوف يسمح لك بالرحيل؟
You absolutely cannot go tomorrow.
لا يمكنك الذهاب غدًا على الإطلاق.
I'll arrange for you to leave as soon as possible.
سأرتب لك المغادرة في أقرب وقت ممكن.
Leave the Song family to me.
اترك عائلة سونغ لي.
Lin Yun.
لين يون.
I already said at Xianhe Restaurant,
لقد قلت بالفعل في مطعم Xianhe،
we're just partners.
نحن مجرد شركاء.
Now, in your current state,
الآن، في حالتك الحالية،
do you still look like the boss of the Chengyun Society?
هل لا تزال تبدو وكأنك رئيس جمعية تشنغيون؟
Song Zhichu only knows I'm not Xu Yin,
سونغ تشيتشو يعرف فقط أنني لست شو ين،
he doesn't know I'm Liang Yi.
إنه لا يعرف أنني ليانغ يي.
I must go tomorrow.
يجب أن أذهب غدا.
Take some medicine before we go.
خذ بعض الدواء قبل أن نذهب.
Even if we're just partners,
حتى لو كنا مجرد شركاء،
I have a duty to protect you.
من واجبي أن أحميك.
♪Raise the big screen, start your pretentious performance♪
♪ارفع الشاشة الكبيرة، وابدأ أدائك المتكلف♪
(Song Zhichu.)
(أغنية تشيتشو.)
(Today I will expose your hypocritical mask.)
(اليوم سأكشف قناعك المنافق)
(I'll make your dirty deeds known to all.)
(سأجعل أفعالك القذرة معروفة للجميع.)
♪You pretend to be innocent, yet the red wounds are vivid in my mind♪
♪تتظاهر بالبراءة، لكن الجروح الحمراء واضحة في ذهني♪
♪Such a hypocritical gift♪
♪هذه هدية منافقة♪
♪Victory is revealed too quickly♪
♪النصر يتكشف بسرعة كبيرة♪
♪Raise the big screen, start your pretentious performance♪
♪ارفع الشاشة الكبيرة، وابدأ أدائك المتكلف♪
♪The most foolish gambler♪
♪المقامر الأكثر حماقة♪
♪Would treat love as prey, caring nothing♪
♪أعامل الحب كفريسة، لا أهتم بأي شيء♪
♪You pretend to be innocent, yet the red wounds are vivid in my mind♪
♪تتظاهر بالبراءة، لكن الجروح الحمراء واضحة في ذهني♪
♪Such a hypocritical gift♪
♪هذه هدية منافقة♪
♪Victory is revealed too quickly♪
♪النصر يتكشف بسرعة كبيرة♪
♪I treated you as my salvation♪
♪لقد عاملتك كخلاصي♪
♪You treated me as a toy♪
♪لقد عاملتني كلعبة♪
♪And we both fall into endless loneliness♪
♪وكلا منا سقط في الوحدة التي لا نهاية لها♪
♪I loved too deeply♪
♪لقد أحببت بعمق شديد♪
♪Your methods are too cruel♪
♪طرقك قاسية جدًا♪
♪Once devotion is desecrated, only waiting for your disgrace♪
♪بمجرد تدنيس الإخلاص، لن تنتظر سوى عارك♪
♪I treated you as my salvation♪
♪لقد عاملتك كخلاصي♪
♪You treated me as a toy♪
♪لقد عاملتني كلعبة♪
♪And we both fall into endless loneliness♪
♪وكلا منا سقط في الوحدة التي لا نهاية لها♪
♪I loved too deeply♪
♪لقد أحببت بعمق شديد♪
♪Your methods are too cruel♪
♪طرقك قاسية جدًا♪
♪Once devotion is desecrated, only waiting for your disgrace♪
♪بمجرد تدنيس الإخلاص، لن تنتظر سوى عارك♪
♪Curtain call♪
♪استدعاء الستار♪